<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eclipse BaSyx</title>
    <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eclipse BaSyx</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 10:08:18 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 10:08:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;col-md-7&#34;&gt;
    &lt;p style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt;
    
       &lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
            &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/kx2F5E5foLU&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
   
 &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;col-md-5&#34;&gt;
    &lt;p style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;block&#34;&gt;
          &lt;p class=&#34;lead&#34;&gt;
            Eclipse BaSyx is the open source implementation of the key concepts defined by Platform Industrie 4.0, such as the Asset Administration Shell. 
            It provides extendable software development kits for Java, C++, and C#.
            &lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;p class=&#34;lead&#34;&gt;
            The Eclipse BaSyx platform addresses challenges such as changeable production to enable individualized goods, exploiting big data analytics and connecting heterogeneous devices and systems while minimizing downtime and other associated costs.
            &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 09:46:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/resources/</guid>
      <description> GitHub Repositories  Eclipse Kuksa IDE: https://github.com/eclipse/kuksa.ide Eclipse Kuksa Apps: https://github.com/eclipse/kuksa.apps Eclipse Kuksa Cloud: https://github.com/eclipse/kuksa.cloud Eclipse Kuksa In-Vehicle: https://github.com/eclipse/kuksa.invehicle Eclipse Kuksa Integration: https://github.com/eclipse/kuksa.integration Eclipse Kuksa Website: https://github.com/eclipse/kuksa.website  Documentations  Eclipse Che Kuksa IDE: https://gitlab-pages.idial.institute/pedro.cuadrachamorro/kuksa-ide/ Rover Docs: https://app4mc-rover.github.io/rover-docs/ Rover API: https://app4mc-rover.github.io/rover-app/ Rover Telemetry UI https://github.com/app4mc-rover/rover-telemetry-ui Eclipse Kuksa Wiki: https://wiki.eclipse.org/Kuksa  Builds  Website Jenkins: https://jenkins.eclipse.org/kuksa/  APPSTACLE Deliverables and more  Available at: https://itea3.org/project/appstacle.html  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forum</title>
      <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/forum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 09:45:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/forum/</guid>
      <description>Visit the Eclipse BaSyx Forum Click Here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 09:24:09 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/calendar/</guid>
      <description>Meet the AGILE team at the following events:
 Click on the Agenda tab to visualize the events as a list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changeable Production To Enable Profitable Lot Size 1</title>
      <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/use-case/changeableproduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/use-case/changeableproduction/</guid>
      <description>Current production industry is designed for large lot sizes. Due to the shorter product lifecycles, manufacturing industry needs to shift its focus. Rapidly changing market requirements demand efficient changeable production processes. Furthermore, customers are increasingly attracted to tailored products that yield a much higher value creation than mass-produced goods. A major challenge for process changes is the necessary reprogramming of Programmable Logic Controllers (PLC). PLCs implement automation programs that execute pre-programmed sequences, optionally supporting a pre-defined amount of flexibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting IT And Production Devices On The Shop-Floor</title>
      <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/use-case/connectingitwithproductiondevices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/use-case/connectingitwithproductiondevices/</guid>
      <description>Walking around the shop-floor to manually query machine states is inefficient and prevents operators from efficiently obtaining a holistic view on the complete production process. Streaming of live production data to IT on the office-floor remains a challenge that prevents efficient monitoring and understanding of production processes.  The BaSyx Virtual Automation Bus (VAB) enables machine to machine communication across the layers of the automation pyramid; shop-floor devices can directly interact with enterprise resource planning (ERP) systems, even if they use different protocols.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/contact/</guid>
      <description>Get involved in the BaSyx project Download the Eclipse BaSyx reference implementation and explore the platform. We have detailed documentation on the wiki. Contact us or visit the forum</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enabler For New Business Models</title>
      <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/use-case/newbusinessmodels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/use-case/newbusinessmodels/</guid>
      <description>Industrie 4.0 is about more efficient mass-production processes, and mass-customization, the efficient and inexpensive production of small lot sizes. Industrie 4.0 is also the end-to-end digitalization of manufacturing and enables new business models. The following exemplary Industrie 4.0 business models can be implemented with Eclipse BaSyx. Data BrokeringData produced in manufacturing processes is extremely valuable for equipment manufacturers and other third-party businesses since it enables prediction and optimization of manufacturing processes and product quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enabler Of Big Data Analytics</title>
      <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/use-case/bigdataanalytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/use-case/bigdataanalytics/</guid>
      <description>Every factory device creates a continuous stream of data. Data analytics can provide valuable insights into production processes: Which variables have impacts on production cost and quality? How can we predict production performance? Where is hidden potential for optimization in my manufacturing processes?   Data analytics requires the combination of data from different sources, i.e. production devices, as well as IT servers. The ability of Eclipse BaSyx to structure machine and product data in Asset Administration Shells, enriching both with semantic information, then combining them, is the enabler for big data analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predictive Maintenance</title>
      <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/use-case/predictivemaintenance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/use-case/predictivemaintenance/</guid>
      <description>Repairing a device once it’s ‘broken’ can lead to unpredictable and expensive downtime. Scheduled maintenance improves the situation, but a static maintenance schedule can cause unnecessary interruptions. In the worst case, required parts need to be ordered, extending downtimes significantly. Predictive maintenance solves these issues: Combining live sensor data and past experience enables prediction of necessary maintenance activities and schedules. Production processes can then be adapted to synchronize and integrate maintenance activities with the least possible impact.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>