<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eclipse BaSyx</title>
    <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eclipse BaSyx</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction (00:18:16)</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/videos/video1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/videos/video1/</guid>
      <description>This video provides an overview about the vision and main concepts of the Industry 4.0.
 What is a Digital Twin Overview of the Asset Administration Shell Overview of the Asset Administration Shell Submodels Industry 4.0 Context in Germany Details about the AAS (Part 1) Eclipse BaSyx - Core Building Blocks Eclipse BaSyx - About SDK  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZF Friedrichshafen AG</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/success-stories/01_zf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/success-stories/01_zf/</guid>
      <description>More Flexible and faster commissioning with Eclipse BaSyx ZF Friedrichshafen AG took the chance to use the most advanced Industry 4.0 operating system when updating their prototype manufacturing line. Now, changing the automated manufacturing process can happen in only a few minutes. This efficient adaptation enables the efficient production also of smallest lot sizes. Furthermore, the integration of new devices into the process is now 30% percent faster, compared to the traditional automation used before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bosch Rexroth AG </title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/success-stories/02_boschrexroth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/success-stories/02_boschrexroth/</guid>
      <description>Next generation manufacturing with Eclipse BaSyx Robert Bosch GmbH was involved from the beginning in the development of the Eclipse BaSyx middleware. The Bosch Customer Experience Center CU.BE in Ulm showcases the potential of Eclipse BaSyx together with revolutionary solutions of Robert Bosch GmbH and Bosch Rexroth AG to realize next generation manufacturing.
The Bosch Customer Experience Center showcases the potentials of the Asset Administration Shell, as well as the ability to control factory workflows with Business Process Model Notation (BPMN), which adds great flexibility to manufacturing processes and enables rapid changes in processes, as well as the efficient integration of new devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OTS Components (00:53:08)</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/videos/video2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/videos/video2/</guid>
      <description>Off-the-shelf (OTS) components are designed and implemented for users which don&amp;rsquo;t want to run BaSyx source code, instead it is possible to run it directly as Docker containers. These OTS components are based on the Eclipse BaSyx Java implementation.
In this video, the main OTS components are introduced and explained:
 How to start the components How to configure their features using property files How to configure their features using environment variables  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code Examples (01:02:09)</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/videos/video3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/videos/video3/</guid>
      <description>Eclipse BaSyx consists of multiple SDKs that can be utilized as a library in your Industry 4.0 applications. This video showcases some common code examples using the Java SDK.
 How to load Maven dependencies How to load the Java SDK in Eclipse IDE Registry Component Using MongoDB for persistency Using Connected ASSManager to query Submodel properties  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sartorius Lab Instruments GmbH &amp; Co. KG</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/success-stories/03_sartorius/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/success-stories/03_sartorius/</guid>
      <description>Leveraging Eclipse BaSyx and Asset Administration Shells for a modular und flexible production Sartorius is a global leader in supplying pharmaceutical and laboratory equipment, covering the segments of bioprocess solutions as well as lab products &amp; services. Sartorius is manufacturing a high number of variants and thus are faced with a multitude of related requirements on their production system. New variants must be easily incorporated; extensions must be modular and seamlessly integrable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extended Use (00:26:09)</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/videos/video4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/videos/video4/</guid>
      <description>This video showcases:
 How to display AAS life-data in a Dashboard? This is realized by an integration with Streamsheets. The illustrated example can be found in Eclipse BaSyx GitHub repository. How to push life-data into the AAS Submodels? This is possible by using the BaSyx component DataBridge, which enables the connectivity with many different communication protocols. This example is based on MQTT Events.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SICK AG</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/success-stories/04_sick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/success-stories/04_sick/</guid>
      <description>Creating a harmonized data space for an efficient intra-logistics SICK is one of the world&#39;s leading suppliers of sensor solutions for automation applications in factories, logistics and processes. As a technology and market leader, SICK creates the basis for safe and efficient control of processes, protection of people from accidents and prevention of environmental damage with sensor intelligence and application solutions.
SICK controls its intra-logistics using event-based dynamic dispatching with the aim of increasing efficiency and flexibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Objective Partner AG</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/success-stories/05_objectivepartner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/success-stories/05_objectivepartner/</guid>
      <description>Asset-as-a-Service with Eclipse BaSyx The objective partner AG is a technology consulting company located in Weinheim. Over the past years, objective partner AG has developed a substantial expertise in implementing Eclipse BaSyx-based solutions for their clients, leveraging the middleware to build customized, scalable, and secure industrial automation systems.
During Hannover Messe 2022, Objective Partner showcased a Corona Test Robot that can autonomously perform nasal swabs for corona rapid tests. The robot solution for Covid tests was realized together with SAP Franka Emika GmbH.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META-LEVEL Software AG</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/success-stories/06_metalevel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/success-stories/06_metalevel/</guid>
      <description>AAS Designer to create, manage and share Asset Administration Shells META-LEVEL is a software company located in Saarbrücken. They develop custom software and provide consulting services for customers from different domains. As experts for Eclipse BaSyx, they are happy to support all your automation needs. One of the major solutions provided by Meta-Level for industrial automation is the AAS Designer.
The AAS Designer is a web-based tool that supports users in creating Asset Administration Shells and associated sub models easily and quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ellenberger GmbH &amp; Co KG</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/success-stories/07_ellenberger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/success-stories/07_ellenberger/</guid>
      <description>Realization of service-based production with Eclipse BaSyx Realization of service-based production with Eclipse BaSyx - Ellenberger GmbH &amp; co. KG is a mechanical parts manufacturing company located in Kaiserslautern. They need to quickly process large numbers of customer orders with different lot sizes based on their capacities and available resources. Eclipse BaSyx Asset Administration Shells were used to integrate an ERP system that automates the decision-making process.
Ellenberger did use Eclipse BaSyx to create Digital Twins for manufacturing islands, machines, and tools and thus enable semi-automatic resource-based feasibility checks based on real-time production data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HÄFNER Präzisionsteile Oberrot GmbH</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/success-stories/08_hafner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/success-stories/08_hafner/</guid>
      <description>System modernisation and data exchange with the help of Eclipse BaSyx HÄFNER Präzisionsteile Oberrot GmbH is a producer of high-precision weights in individual to small series production. Some of these weights are highly customised. Weights are regularly recalibrated in addition to the initial calibration, whereby the interval is determined by customers. The company also produces precision parts (e.g. for gearboxes), about which various data are recorded in a CAQ system (Computer-Aided Quality) during quality assurance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Industry 4.0 becomes practical</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/blog/2021/02/17/industry40becomespractical/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/blog/2021/02/17/industry40becomespractical/</guid>
      <description>Fraunhofer IESE brings flexible manufacturing to companies with Eclipse BaSyx. One of the goals of industry 4.0 is to be able to exchange devices with the same capabilities in a production plant without having to change the control system. The BaSys 4.0 project, funded by the German Federal Ministry of Education and Research, aims to solve this challenge in a practical way with the concept of service-based manufacturing. With the help of the Eclipse BaSyx, Fraunhofer IESE from Kaiserslautern and other project partners enable even small and medium-sized companies to make convertible manufacturing a reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shopfloor 4.0</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/offer/shopfloor40/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/offer/shopfloor40/</guid>
      <description>Fraunhofer IESE is offering an off-the-shelf Industrie 4.0 solution based on Eclipse BaSyx with its partners NetApp and objective partner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 09:46:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/resources/</guid>
      <description> GitHub Repositories  Eclipse Kuksa IDE: https://github.com/eclipse/kuksa.ide Eclipse Kuksa Apps: https://github.com/eclipse/kuksa.apps Eclipse Kuksa Cloud: https://github.com/eclipse/kuksa.cloud Eclipse Kuksa In-Vehicle: https://github.com/eclipse/kuksa.invehicle Eclipse Kuksa Integration: https://github.com/eclipse/kuksa.integration Eclipse Kuksa Website: https://github.com/eclipse/kuksa.website  Documentations  Eclipse Che Kuksa IDE: https://gitlab-pages.idial.institute/pedro.cuadrachamorro/kuksa-ide/ Rover Docs: https://app4mc-rover.github.io/rover-docs/ Rover API: https://app4mc-rover.github.io/rover-app/ Rover Telemetry UI https://github.com/app4mc-rover/rover-telemetry-ui Eclipse Kuksa Wiki: https://wiki.eclipse.org/Kuksa  Builds  Website Jenkins: https://jenkins.eclipse.org/kuksa/  APPSTACLE Deliverables and more  Available at: https://itea3.org/project/appstacle.html  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forum</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/forum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 09:45:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/forum/</guid>
      <description>Visit the Eclipse BaSyx Forum Click Here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 09:24:09 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/calendar/</guid>
      <description>Meet the AGILE team at the following events:
 Click on the Agenda tab to visualize the events as a list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/about/</guid>
      <description>What is BaSyx Eclipse BaSyx is the open source platform for next generation automation. It implements key concepts defined by Platform Industrie 4.0, such as the Asset Administration Shell as standardized digital twin. Our mission is to provide a free software platform that enables all interested parties, large and small companies, research institutes, academia, and interested persons, to participate in and to shape the fourth industrial revolution. We believe that the availability of a free reference technology platform is a key success factor for the Industrie 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Architecture</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/architecture/</guid>
      <description>Digital Twins with Asset Administration Shells  Eclipse BaSyx uses the Asset Administration Shell (AAS) as base technology for digital twins. The AAS is the digital identity of an asset and links to AAS sub models that provide asset specific information, simulation models, and services. Eclipse BaSyx supports three kinds of sub models. The same AAS may link to any number of each kind:
 Static sub models provide access to data that only changes seldomly, such as documents, electronic certificates, data sheets, and digital name plates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BaSyx How-To - Asset Integration</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/asset_integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/asset_integration/</guid>
      <description>Asset Integration Example Overview  Docker Java C# C++ Python  Docker AAS Web GUI Java In the following, device integration with BaSyx as implemented in the Device Integration Example on Github is considered using a heating element. The heating element has a simple interface:
 A heating setpoint can be configured in degrees Fahrenheit via http/REST. The last configured setpoint can be queried via http/REST. Every second, the currently measured temperature value in degrees Fahrenheit is made available as an MQTT event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benefits</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/benefits/</guid>
      <description>End-to-End Digitization End-to-end digitization integrates all assets into one virtual space. It realizes a holistic digital twin that covers all kinds of assets – for example devices, products, and processes. This enables virtualization and optimization of individual assets, manufacturing plants, and whole supply chains.
Lot Size 1 Production Changes in automation processes requires developers to adapt PLC programs, MES components, and requires the testing of all changes. Every problem that occurs delays the re-start of a production line, and is therefore highly expensive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concepts</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/concepts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/concepts/</guid>
      <description>Digital Twins Digital Twins are complete representations of any physical or non-physical real-world asset. They represent the current state of the asset though a harmonized interface, which covers for example the state of an asset, and sensor values. Digital twins also provide simulation models that predict asset behavior in a particular situation, provide evidences for substantiated decisions, and enable what-if analysis.
The Asset Administration shell is an agreed technical foundation for digital twins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/contact/</guid>
      <description>Get involved in the BaSyx project Download the Eclipse BaSyx reference implementation and explore the platform. We have detailed documentation on the wiki. Contact us or visit the forum</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digitization</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/digitization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/digitization/</guid>
      <description>Our mission is to simplify the digitization of production environments. Eclipse BaSyx provides a robust and scalable infrastructure for digital twins, and integrate numerous applications that support many kinds of digitization tasks. This includes components to create, monitor, and host Asset Administration Shells (AAS), integrate them with their real-world assets and provide easy-to-use dashboards. The Eclipse BaSyx Data Bridge connects AAS with assets to create Digital Twins that represent the asset state at all times, and optionally enables controlling of assets and processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/overview/</guid>
      <description>Making the Industry 4.0 happen requires great efforts and strong cooperation between research, academia, industry, the public, and standardization bodies. And it requires an implementation – the code that runs the world of manufacturing. Eclipse BaSyx emerged as commonly used Industry 4.0 middleware and became one of the first implementations of the Asset Administration Shell (AAS), even before it was a standard for digital twins. This is why Eclipse BaSyx is part of the code that enables digitization of manufacturing – that connects machines and IT systems – that runs our world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partners</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/basyx/partners/</guid>
      <description>table { font-family: arial, sans-serif; border-collapse: collapse; width: 100%; } td, th { border: 1px solid #eeeeee; text-align: left; padding: 6px; } tr:nth-child(even) { background-color: #eeeeee; }  Eclipse BaSyx Partners Eclipse BaSyx is supported by an ecosystem of professional companies and research partners which would be happy to assist you in your projects.
-- System Concept &amp; Strategic Consulting  Industry 4.0 will drive a significant change in your system architecture.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>