<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eclipse BaSyx</title>
    <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eclipse BaSyx</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Industry 4.0 becomes practical</title>
      <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/blog/2021/02/17/industry40becomespractical/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/blog/2021/02/17/industry40becomespractical/</guid>
      <description>Fraunhofer IESE brings flexible manufacturing to companies with Eclipse BaSyx. One of the goals of industry 4.0 is to be able to exchange devices with the same capabilities in a production plant without having to change the control system. The BaSys 4.0 project, funded by the German Federal Ministry of Education and Research, aims to solve this challenge in a practical way with the concept of service-based manufacturing. With the help of the Eclipse BaSyx, Fraunhofer IESE from Kaiserslautern and other project partners enable even small and medium-sized companies to make convertible manufacturing a reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shopfloor 4.0</title>
      <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/offer/shopfloor40/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/offer/shopfloor40/</guid>
      <description>Fraunhofer IESE is offering an off-the-shelf Industrie 4.0 solution based on Eclipse BaSyx with its partners NetApp and objective partner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 10:08:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/about/</guid>
      <description>Eclipse BaSyx is the open source platform for next generation automation. It implements key concepts defined by Platform Industrie 4.0, such as the Asset Administration Shell as standardized digital twin. Our mission is to provide a free software platform that enables all interested parties, large and small companies, research institutes, academia, and interested persons, to participate in and to shape the fourth industrial revolution. We believe that the availability of a free reference technology platform is a key success factor for the Industrie 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributing to Eclipse BaSyx</title>
      <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/contributing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 09:46:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/contributing/</guid>
      <description>Get in touch ! There is the
BaSyx-dev mailing list and a bi-weekly Zoom meeting every Thursday on even calendar weeks from 1-2pm (CET/CEST). How to contribute to Eclipse BaSyx Great that you are interested in contributing to Eclipse BaSyx. We really looking forward to receive your contribution!
In the project we agreed upon the following approach to add contributions to the project.
 Meet the Definition of Done (DoD) A review took place for the code The new feature was at least once tested manually, deployed to a running test instance Clearly outline third party dependencies  Definition of Done First, we have DoD for solved issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 09:46:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/resources/</guid>
      <description> GitHub Repositories  Eclipse Kuksa IDE: https://github.com/eclipse/kuksa.ide Eclipse Kuksa Apps: https://github.com/eclipse/kuksa.apps Eclipse Kuksa Cloud: https://github.com/eclipse/kuksa.cloud Eclipse Kuksa In-Vehicle: https://github.com/eclipse/kuksa.invehicle Eclipse Kuksa Integration: https://github.com/eclipse/kuksa.integration Eclipse Kuksa Website: https://github.com/eclipse/kuksa.website  Documentations  Eclipse Che Kuksa IDE: https://gitlab-pages.idial.institute/pedro.cuadrachamorro/kuksa-ide/ Rover Docs: https://app4mc-rover.github.io/rover-docs/ Rover API: https://app4mc-rover.github.io/rover-app/ Rover Telemetry UI https://github.com/app4mc-rover/rover-telemetry-ui Eclipse Kuksa Wiki: https://wiki.eclipse.org/Kuksa  Builds  Website Jenkins: https://jenkins.eclipse.org/kuksa/  APPSTACLE Deliverables and more  Available at: https://itea3.org/project/appstacle.html  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forum</title>
      <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/forum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 09:45:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/forum/</guid>
      <description>Visit the Eclipse BaSyx Forum Click Here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 09:24:09 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/calendar/</guid>
      <description>Meet the AGILE team at the following events:
 Click on the Agenda tab to visualize the events as a list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/contact/</guid>
      <description>Get involved in the BaSyx project Download the Eclipse BaSyx reference implementation and explore the platform. We have detailed documentation on the wiki. Contact us or visit the forum</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://staging.eclipse.org/basyx/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>